So this Black History Month, let's talk about some things I don't play about.
One, Black popular culture.
Two, Black love.
I want to see us in partnership.
And in order for that, we need to have three, therapy.
And so I bring to you the founders of Therapy for Black Men to talk to you about what they need from us to keep doing the work they do.
Good morning, everyone. I'm Vladimir Kaliksy.
And I'm Benjamin Kaliksy.
We're the founders of Therapy for Black Men.
So if you've been on our page, you know that last week we made the very tough announcement that we will be closing Therapy for Black Men.
And since then, there has been a GoFundMe page created by Lisa Sugarman on our behalf so that we can reach our goal of $350,000 so that we can serve our Black men and boys.
So please, if you are unable to donate, kindly share our links, kindly share our support, our work page, which is on our page, because every little bit helps.
And we thank you for the swell of support.
We're immensely grateful for that.
Although we're not quite there yet, we can see the light at the end of the tunnel now.
And we thank you for that.
And we will keep you posted as we move along.
Thank you so much.